

SHAKIR SULTANOV

Fullstack developer

I am a hard working and ambitious person with a positive mindset and a never ending desire to continuously learn and grow professionally. Along my academic and self-educational journey, I have had the opportunity to explore various areas of IT working on a variety of projects. I am passionate about further expanding my experience and skills to become a highly skilled and successful developer.



Ukrainian, S Permit



31.03.2000



sultanovshakir12@gmail.com



+41 76 454 7413



Tösstalstrasse 74, 8636 Wald ZH



<u>LinkedIn</u>



Portfolio



GitHub

LANGUAGES

English Russian Ukrainian Turkish German B2 Native Native Native A2

EDUCATION

09.2018 - 07.2022

Bachelor of Computer Engineering – Odesa Mechnikov National University, Odesa, Ukraine

- Programming fundamentals
- Computer Engineering fundamentals
- Data structures and algorithms
- Computer networks
- Operating systems
- Web and mobile development

04.2024 - 07.2024

Powercoders Bootcamp - ICT Work Integration Program

- Foundations in HTML, CSS,
 JavaScript
- Weekly business & social skills training (teamwork, communication, management)

REFERENCE

Kenneth Ritley

Prof. Dr. Kenneth Ritley, Dozent, BFH

kenneth.ritley@bfh.ch https://ritley.com/ +41 79 509 57 22

SKILLS

ADVANCED

JavaScript, HTML, CSS

INTERMEDIATE

Vue.js, Angular, Python, FastAPI, PostgreSQL, Git, Docker

BEGINNER

Spring Boot

BASIC

Java, C#, Android Studio, Figma, Gitlab, CI/CD

EXPERIENCE

08.2024 - present

Fullstack Developer (Praktikant), BFH, Biel/Bienne, Switzerland

- Worked on various non-commercial projects.
- Developed both frontend and backend solutions based on project requirements.
- · Had experience working with Docker
- Contributed to implementing business logic and ensuring functionality.
- Managed GitLab repositories and CI/CD pipelines for development and deployment.
- Participated in meetings with product owners and stakeholders to align project goals and requirements.

11.2022 - 07.2023

Frontender, Part-time Freelance, Odesa, Ukraine

• Responsible for design and frontend development

02.2018 - 01.2021

Seller-loader, LLC "7th Kilometer", Odesa, Ukraine

- Responsible for loading
- Organize warehouse inventory efficiently
- Responsibly fulfill customer orders

HOBBIES

Read

I love reading psychological books, books to understand life, people, and the world.

Music

Love to listen to music when I am working on something, especially violin.